Guide to the Living Stage records 1965-2001
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 2: Artistic and workshop files, 1966-2001
  - Production reports and workshops, 1967-2001
    - Production Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Production Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Production Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Production Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Production Reports and Jams, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Production Reports I, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Production Reports I, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Production Reports II, 1982-1983 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Production Reports II, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Production Reports Vol. 2, 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Production Reports Vol. 2, 1990-1991 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Program Evaluation - Fairhill and Sharpe Health Schools, 1978-1979 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Program Evaluations, 1988-1989 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Program Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Project and Workshop Evaluations for Grants, 1986-1988 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Project Evaluations, 1978-1982 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Project Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Project Evaluations, 1983-1984 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Project Evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Project Evaluations, 1985-1986 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Project Evaluations, 1986-1987 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Project Evaluations, 1987-1988 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Public Performance, May 9, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Public Performance/Associate Event, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Rehearsal Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Rehearsal Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Residency Sessions Notes Vol. I, 1987-1993 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Residency Sessions Notes Vol. I, 1987-1993 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Residency Sessions Notes Vol. II, 1987-1989 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Residency Sessions Notes Vol. II, 1987-1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Roosevelt Seniors, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - School Evaluations, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - School Evaluations, 1979-1981 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Season Evaluation, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Season Evaluations, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Season Evaluations, 1982-1983 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Season Evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Season Evaluations, 1986-1987 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Season Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Season Evaluations by Jennifer Nelson, 1991-1992 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Season Evaluations of Special Products, 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Season Reports I, 1983-1984 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Sharpe Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Sharpe Health School Evaluations, 1982-1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Sharpe Evaluations, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Sharpe Health Season Evaluation, 1993-1994 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - South Carolina Workshop, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Special Targeting, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Summer Children's Theatre, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Summer Program, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Summer Workshops, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Summer Workshop Flyer (Human Beings), 1980 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Summer Workshops, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Summer Workshops, 1984 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Summer Workshop Scholarships, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Summer Workshops, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Summer Workshops, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Summer Workshops, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Summer Workshops, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Summer Workshops, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Summer Workshops, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Summer Workshops, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Summer Workshops, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Summer Workshop Song Repertoire, Undated (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Teen Mom's Production Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Teen Mothers Evaluations, 1993-1994 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Theatre Communications Group, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Theatre for Children and Youth, 1968-1969 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Themes for Age Groups, Undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - TIP Workshop Correspondence, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - TMOT Evaluation - Marty Boyer, 1991-1992 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - TMOT Evaluations, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Various Short Term Workshops, Undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Various Workshop Backgrounds, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Wakefield P.S, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Washington Free School Evaluation, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Weekend Workshop, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - White House Conference on Handicapped Individuals, April 1977 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Woodson Sr and Jr High Evaluations, 1981-1982 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Workshop Material, 1967-1968 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Workshops, 1968-1973 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Workshop Quotes, 1969-1971 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Workshop Material, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Workshop Inquiries, 1970-1971 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Workshops, 1970-1972 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Workshop III, 1971 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Workshops IV, 1972-1973 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Workshops and Awards, 1974-1982 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Workshop Correspondence, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Workshops V, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Workshops, 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Workshop Schedule, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Workshop Information, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Workshop/Performance Letters - Discontinued, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Workshops, 1978-1981 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Workshop, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Workshop Fund Letter, 1983-1984 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Workshop Letter/Questionnaire, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Workshop Ad, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Workshop Budget, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Workshop Summaries, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Workshops, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Workshops - General, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Workshops Schedules, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Workshop Evaluations, 1986-1989 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Workshop Budget, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Workshop Summaries and Analysis, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Workshops General, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Workshop Flyers, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Workshop Request Template, Undated (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Workshops VII, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Year End Reports, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - You and Me Workshop, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Production files and scripts, 1967-2000
    - Articles - Resources/References, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Benefit Songs 4 Keys, November 1987 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Bibliographies for Production Research, Circa 1970s (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Calendar, 1985-1989 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Chuckle Dust Caper, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - CSP - Raps and Scripts, 1985-1986 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Every Heart in the House, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Handbook of Jams, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Images and Longstreet, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Images Script, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Images Work in Progress, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Improvisation for the Theatre - Viola Spolin, Undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Jams, 1973-1978 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      Copyright 1978
    - Jams, 1978-1981 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Jams, 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Jams (Copyright 1978), 1973-1978 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Jams Index, 1978-1981 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Kenneth Wooden - Weeping in the Playtime of Others, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Living Stage and The Creative Process, Undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Living Stage Artistic Process, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Living Stage High School Program, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Longstreet Script, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Lorton Poetry, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Lovers of Living Stage - Candide, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Magazines - Resources/References, circa 1970s (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Magazines - Resources/References, circa 1970s (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Marvel, Fantasy, and Education Pieces, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Performances, 1969-1981 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Performances, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      Folder 1 of 4
    - Performances, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      Folder 2 of 4
    - Performances, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      Folder 3 of 4
    - Performances, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      Folder 4 of 4
    - Performances Master List, 1969-1983 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Pieces for Tours, 1985-1986 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Pieces, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Pieces - Drugs, Imagination, War, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Poems and Songs for Lynched Hopes, Undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Program Fact Sheets, 1998-1999 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Public Performances - Basta!Basta!, 1984-1985 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Restoration, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Restoration, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Restoration, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Restoration, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Restoration - Percussion, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Restoration - Percussion, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Restoration - Piano/Conductor, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Restoration - Piano/Conductor, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Restoration - Vocal, 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Robert Alexander (Plays, Poems), 1970 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Score to Tape of L.S. Jams (from which the copy was made for copyright purposes), 1973-1978 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Screenplay- The Murder of Children's Dreams, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Script, 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Script and Song Book, 1977-1978 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Scripts, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Teen Mom Scripts, 1991-1995 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - The Crystal Chapter, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - The Crystal Chapter, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Violence Poems, Undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Written Materials - Scripts and Jams, 1985-1986 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Series 3: Audiovisual materials, 1967-1998
  Series 3. Audiovisual Materials (1967-1998) includes all photos, negatives, and film of the Living Stage or their productions. It is divided into three subseries. Subseries 3.1 Photographic Materials includes various photos and negatives showing the cast of the Living Stage at various times as well as production stills. Unfortunately, the majority of these documents are undated or have little in the way of description. Subseries 3.2 Reel to Reel Materials includes tapings of various workshops and productions mostly from the 1970s and 1980s. Subseries 3.3 Cassete and VHS tapes contains cassette, VHS, Betamax, and U-matic tapes either used by the Living Stage for performances or made by/about the Living Stage.
  - Photographic materials, 1967-1998
    - Bob Alexander Photos, late 1960s (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Bob's Workshop Photos, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Chuckledust Photos, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Company Group Photo-Blow-ups, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Company Group Photos, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Company Group Photos, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Company Group Photos, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Danny Dither Photos, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Images Photos, 1984-1987 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Improvisational Workshop Photos, 1968-1969 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Labeled Photos, 1980s (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Living Stage Company, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Living Stage Company, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Living Stage Company, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Living Stage Company, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Living Stage Company, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Living Stage Theatre Company Rendering by Eric Colbert AIA, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Longstreet Photos, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Lynched Hopes and Unsung Dreams Photos, 1991-1992 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Labeled Photos, 1992-1998 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Photocopies of Labeled Photos, 1992-1998 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Photos, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Photos, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Negatives, Undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Negatives Roll - 1428-3 Drake, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Negatives Roll - 1428-4 Drake, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Negatives Roll - 1428-5 Drake, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Negatives Roll - 1452-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Negatives Roll - 1452-3, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Negatives Roll - 1452-4, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Negatives Roll - 1452-5, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Negatives Roll - 1452-6, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Negatives Roll - 1611-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Negatives Roll - 1611-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Negatives Roll - 5496-1 Miller Bob Alexander, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Negatives Roll - 5496-2 Miller, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Negatives Roll - 5496-3 Miller, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Negatives Roll - 5496-4 Miller, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Negatives Roll - 5496-5 Miller, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Negatives Roll - 5600-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Negatives Roll - 6715-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Negatives Roll - 6715-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Negatives Roll - 6715-3, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Negatives Roll - 6715-4, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Negatives Roll - 6716-1 Al Miller, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Negatives Roll - 6873-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Negatives Roll - 6955-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Negatives Roll - 6955-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Negatives Roll - 6955-3, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Negatives Roll - 6955-4, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Negatives Roll - 7146-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Negatives Roll - 7146-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Negatives Roll - 7146-3, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 30)
    - Negatives Roll - 7146-4, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 31)
    - Negatives Roll - 8313-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 32)
    - Negatives Roll - 8313-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 33)
    - Negatives Roll - 8313-3, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 34)
    - Negatives Roll - 8313-4, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 35)
    - Negatives Roll - 8659-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 36)
    - Negatives Roll - 8659-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 37)
    - Negatives Roll - 10455-1 Alexander, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 38)
    - Negatives Roll - 18371-3 Al Miller, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 39)
    - Negatives Roll - 21024-1, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 40)
    - Negatives Roll - 21024-2, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 41)
    - Negatives Roll - 21024-3, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 42)
    - Negatives Roll - 21024-3, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 43)
    - Negatives Roll - 21024-4, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 44)
    - Negatives Roll - 21024-5, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 45)
    - Negatives Roll - 210246, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 46)
    - Negatives Roll - 21024-7, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 88, Folder 47)
    - Photos and Negatives, Undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Pictures, 1980s and 1990s (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Rehearsal Photos, 1986-1992 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, 1967-1968 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Treasure Island Photos, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Wind in the Willows Book, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Wind in the Willows Photos, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Workshop and Actor Photos, circa 1970s or 1980s (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Workshop and Events Photos Including 30th Anniversary, 1970s - 1996 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Reel to Reel Materials, 1977-1985
    - #1 CR 1-3, January 30, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      Large Box
    - 8 [No other label than L.S 8], January 26 (1970s and 1980s) (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Bob A. #3 and Jennifer #2, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Bob Alexander VO #1, January 1984 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      VO 1 of 2
    - Bob Alexander VO #2, January 1984 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      VO 2 of 2
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #3, 4, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #1, 2 R-60, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #11, 12, 13 R-86, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #3, 4 R-62, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #5, 6, 7 R-64, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #5, 6, 7 R-68, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #8, 9, 10, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 21)
      Completely Unraveled - Large Box
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #8, 9, 10 R-67, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" CR #8, 9, 10 R-71, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Comm. Co. - "Fairhill" R #70, February 3, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Comm. Co. - "Living Stage" CR# 1, 2 R-107, March 24, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Comm. Co. - "Living Stage" CR# 9, 10 - R-9, December 1, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Comm. Co. - "St. Mary's" CR #1, 2, 3 R-54, February 2, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Comm. Co. - "St. Mary's" CR #4, 5, 6 R-57, February 2, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 1, 2, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 11, 12 - R-11, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 11, 12 - R-14, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 13, 14 - R-13, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 15, 16 - R-15, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 15, 16 - R-65, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 3-4, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Comm. Co. - CR# 5, 6 R-10, December 1, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Comm. Co. "Living Stage" CR# 7, 8 R-7, December 1, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Comm. Co. "Women" CR# 15, 16 R-105, February 27, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Comm. Co. "Women" CR# 15, 16 R-108, February 27, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - DC CR# 3, 4, February 26, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - DC Jail, February 26, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - DC Jail, CR 1, 2, February 26, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - DC Jail, CR 11-12, February 26, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - DC Jail, CR 13, 14, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - DC Jail, CR 5, 6, February 26, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - DC Jail, CR 7, 8, February 26, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - DC Jail, CR 9-10, February 26, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Durrin Films - Cut Work Print, February 15, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Durrin Films - FDA CR 8, 9, 10, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - F/S, January 3, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      Franklin Sherman?
    - Fairhill - 00-24, November 30, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Fairhill - First 30 min, Tape #2, October 26, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Fairhill - Pix R-2, circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Fairhill - Pix R-3, circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Fairhill - Pix R-5, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Fairhill - Pix R-6, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Fairhill - Tape #1, October 26, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      Continued from October 19, 1977 Tape
    - Fairhill - Tapes I and II, November 2, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Fairhill - Warm-up to 14 and Fairhill 14-30, November 9 and 30, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Fairhill #1, October 19 and 26, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Fairhill #1 and #2, May 3, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Fairhill School - Dear Imagination CR 1, 2, and 3, 29618 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Fairhill School CR #3, 4, 5, February 1, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Fairhill School CR #5, February 1, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Fairhill School CR #7, 8, 9, February 1, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Fairhill School CR 5, 6, 7, February 1, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Fairhill Schools - Interviews with Mothers`, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 93, Folder 10)
      Loose
    - Franklin Sherman, May 2, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      Color?
    - Franklin Sherman - 12/6, F/S, 18-30, January 3, 1978 (Box 94)
    - Franklin Sherman - First Session, 26.4", October 18, 1977 (Box 94)
    - Franklin Sherman - Session 2 - Tapes #1 and #2, November 1, 1977 (Box 94)
    - Its Alright to Cry, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Its Alright to Cry, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Jennifer V/O, January 18, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Kids, January 26, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Kids - "The Spez" CR1 SR1, January 26, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Kids - Rolls 7, 5, 4, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Kids - Rolls 7, 5, 4, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 94)
    - Kids #6, January 26, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Kids #9, January 26, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Kids Box 26, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Kids Pix #1, January 26, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Kids Pix R-2, January 26, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Kids Pix R-3, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Kids Pix R-5, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Kids Pix R6, No Pulls, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Kids Pix R-7, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Kids Pix R-8, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 95, Folder 6)
      Smells like Vinegar
    - Kids SR 4, 5, January 26, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      Semi-Unraveling
    - Lorton - #2, January 22, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Lorton - CR #10-12 No Sculptures, January 22, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Lorton - CR #12-14, No Lunch, January 22, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Lorton - CR #15, January 22, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Lorton - CR #17 - I see now drama poetry for sound make you a lot like God - Talking re poems, January 22, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Lorton - CR #19, No Talking No Singing, January 22, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Lorton - CR #6, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Lorton - CR1 SK1, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Lorton - Pix/Pulls 1-4, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Lorton - Pix/Pulls 5, 6, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Lorton - Pulls from Rolls 8, 9, 10, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Lorton - PX #1, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Lorton - PX #10, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Lorton - PX #11, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Lorton - PX #2, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Lorton - PX #3, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Lorton - PX #4, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Lorton - PX #5, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Lorton - PX #6, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Lorton - PX #7, January 22, 1981 (Box 96)
    - Lorton - PX #8, January 22, 1981 (Box 95 (unboxed), Folder 19)
    - Lorton - PX #9, January 22, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Lorton - Woman Dying - R IV, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - LS #4 - 4P70 CR #10, Circa 1970s to 1980s (Box 95 (unboxed), Folder 24)
    - LS #5, January 30, 1981 (Box 95 (unboxed), Folder 25)
    - LS #7, January 26, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Performance Restraint - SR# 9, November 28, 1980 (Box 97)